Good morning, you guys.
Good morning.
Hey there, San.
Great weather today.
San, dear.
You do eat more than just lunch, don't you?
Yes.
Well, you always look so sickly. It concerns me.
Don't worry, honey. I'll bring you some nori the next chance I get.
Saga's nori is so nutritious.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Good morning to all of you.
Morning, sir.
Ah, look at that. Imari Bay sparkling today. Horseshoe crabs looking lively.
I want you ladies to cook, slice and dry with the kind of pride that the best and only dried squid maker in Kyushu ought to have.
Time for the company song. Let's see. Today our leader is you. Get up here, Tatsumi.
Right.
Good morning.
Let's go.
And so we took to the stage at EFS.
Sadly we sold 500 tickets in a 30,000 seat stadium.
That's like barely over 1%, which means we stopped going up and just bombed.
It would have been weird to do an encore after that.
So we put the new song on the shelf.
Plus the unsolved tickets put us in debt big time.
It stunk, even for zombies!
Could this be the end?
The EFS show was a huge disaster.
But we still want to get on stage together again.
That's why we each picked up part-time jobs
to try and bring ourselves out of the red.
We're not going to give up.
Oh, yeah.
And as for our fearless producer, Mr. Kotaro...
What's that?
Pope's nose?
Why's it called that?
Oh, you want me to save Saga, Your Holiness?
Sorry, it ain't happening!
This is the Saga-pocalypse!
No, it's Saga, get it!
I knew that.
Which is why I was hoping that I could.
This stuff's named after a nose!
Pope's nose!
Man, that's gotta feel bad!
Morning, sir!
I'm Saga's new milk delivery girl!
Don't move!
This stuff is tricky.
I can never seem to master the blend.
It just doesn't look, I don't know, lively enough?
Well, we are dead.
I knew it.
The color is still off.
I sure wish Kotaro was here.
What the hell's the matter with that guy?
I'll go check on him one more time.
Excuse me!
Is he here?
It's me, sir.
Sakura.
Are you okay?
Oh no, why is it so dark?
Because you're way overdue for a haircut.
Oh great, it's you again.
I don't think this is good for your health.
Hey, guess what?
We worked really hard this month,
and we brought in some extra money.
Listen, sir.
Yes, that show is practically a second death sentence for us.
But we rose from the dead once,
and I know that we can do it again.
And when we do, we'll be even stronger.
It's over, and that's that.
No, it isn't.
Now I'm not sure when exactly,
but we will pay off that debt.
No matter how long it might take us,
we'll keep on giving it all we've got.
I'm done.
Just go.
But sir,
we're supposed to be performing at Guile soon,
the metal spot where we debuted.
We thought if we went back there,
maybe Fran Shushu could get a fresh start.
We never sang that last song you wrote us,
so we're gonna do it on that stage.
And I want you to be there, Mr. Kotaro.
Hey, what's the problem?
You nerd.
You're all scrunched up like a pope's nose.
Look at yourself.
Hey, Sakuna, say I'm a chicken butt.
Come on, do it.
It'll be funny.
I wish I knew how to get him back to his old self again.
Yeah, it sounds like he's been on a bender for a solid month now.
He may be a little out there,
but I think it'll be hard to operate without him,
if not impossible.
Hey, girls, I'm just spitballing here.
But what if this isn't about the money?
And perhaps there's something he's been hiding from all of us.
I mean, think about it.
Why did he choose that time for us to perform at EFS?
Good point.
He couldn't have thought the event would sell out.
So, like, he was in a rush maybe?
Why though?
I don't know.
Well then, if Lady Ai is correct,
I think we should try to assist him.
Though we need to discern what the trouble is.
I bet we could figure it out if we went snooping around his office.
It's open.
Hell yeah!
Let's clean him out!
Yay!
Guys, be careful!
Whoa!
Check out all this junk!
Remember not to break anything, okay?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Crap, I'm in trouble!
This is the encore we never got to sing.
It must be a rough draft, huh?
No!
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
La, la, la, la, la, la, la.
I guess this is what his songwriting process is like.
You can tell that he really cares.
Or used to, at least.
We still haven't figured out why he was in such a hurry for us to go big.
Yeah, but now we know how he felt about the EFS show.
Next time we sing, we have to make sure Mr. Kotaro's there.
If we can finally perform that encore song on stage,
then maybe he'll go back to his old self again.
Once he feels better, he'll explain everything.
I'm not sure it'll work, but we should definitely try.
Yeah, and at the next show, that song will knock him right on his ass!
Right!
Ha, ha, ha!
Ha, ha!
Here you are, m'lord.
Reporting in after another grueling day of defending justice in Saga.
I swear, babe, the drinks you pour me at the end of these long shifts are always so sweet.
My pleasure. Thank you for taking such good care of Saga.
Grape, sir.
Uh, just doing my job.
Gorgeous.
I'll keep coming to see you every night.
Your eyes are so arresting.
Kay, I'm here. Where's the party?
My bad.
Lord Kotorou, methinks you've had too much to drink.
What?
I was wrong. I was wrong. I was wrong. I was wrong. So, so wrong. Wrong.
Okay. If we can do that on stage, we're set. Oh, trust me, we're gonna kill it. But, Mr. Kotorou, I guess we never heard anything from the boozer.
After what Yugiri saw last night, it isn't surprising. The poor man was practically coming apart at the seams.
Please don't worry, you guys. Just stay focused on getting ready for the set. I'll go and get him.
The show is tonight. Will you please listen to me?
I told you, do whatever you want.
I'm just asking you to show up. The girls and I love your songs. We want to keep performing them.
I know some bad stuff happened, but that's not a reason for us to quit being idols.
Look, there's nothing more I can do for you.
What happened, Mr. Kotorou? Don't you remember what you said to me back then?
I have what it takes! I'll never, never abandon you!
Where's the old you? Because we need him right now.
He didn't have what it takes.
Whatever! I'm done trying! Forget you!
You guys, we have to make sure this concert is a success, even without a producer.
Yeah, we haven't been here lately. Looks like they've got a totally new crowd.
I'm sure how Fashushi will be all right.
Bit of a rally lot to play after EFS.
Yeah, and that makes this a really important night for them.
All the more reason to show our support.
Indeed!
What? Idols? What the hell?
Fashushi!
Look off, socks off!
Stop wasting our time!
Yeah, get on with it.
This is lame.
Uh, hey guys! We're Fraud Shoo Shoo!
That's them.
See, a little while ago we did a show at EFS that went kind of haywire and we can't let it end like that.
So we're trying to make a comeback starting tonight, right here, right now, okay?
So, uh, thanks for coming to the first stop on our little revenge tour.
You ready to rock?
It's not a big crowd, and it's nothing we haven't done before.
Let's put EFS behind us.
It's okay.
How long do you plan to darken my bar with that pathetic look?
Is the verbal abuse included in the bill?
Most of my customers don't sleep here overnight because they're afraid to go home.
Look, you said that you're done, right?
What was it called again? The Zombie World Super Project?
The Zombieland Saga Project.
Yeah, that.
It was a crazy idea in the first place.
A bunch of undead turned pop stars?
Your Sagaettes will get over it, too.
It'll be a nice memory for them while they wander the earth for eternity.
Their name is Fraun Shoo Shoo.
Zombies don't sing and dance. Let them get on with their lives.
I mean, they're dead, but you know what I'm saying.
This project has a crucial deadline!
After they died on stage, worse than any living idol group ever did,
and then got stuck with a massive debt! There's no way it'll work now! Even you know that!
All right, fine.
You demanded the impossible out of those girls from day one, and they still found a way to make it happen.
So, if this latest hurdle is something you don't believe they can overcome,
well, then you're probably right.
This whole thing started because of your ambition, so you might as well let it end that way, too.
Go sit them down and tell them,
I'm sorry, but I just don't believe in the Sagaettes.
You Sagaettes are all washed up. It's curtains for you.
It's not the Sagaettes!
It's Fraun Shoo Shoo!
Huh. There you go.
Nick!
Oh no, this is ZFS all over again.
That sucked! Get off the stage!
We've got one more song left, numbskull!
Fine, then go sing it somewhere else!
What's the plan? Is your set over?
Should we leave?
No way, we came this far.
Yeah, but they're so angry.
Shit.
Well...
This hurts.
Our group finally got on stage together after so long.
Is this really how it has to end?
He showed up!
One core!
One more number!
Who's this guy?
Cut it out!
One more number!
Hey, say it with me, everybody!
I said quiet!
Oh no!
That was nothing!
Yeah! Encore! Encore! Encore! Encore!
Yeah! Encore!
Nobody asked, you losers!
Damn you!
Ha ha!
It's been a while since we threw down, man!
Right, let's give him what for!
Alright, fine! Let's fight!
I'll handle this easy!
Saki!
Don't just stand there!
Your pop fingers are down!
So sing!
Sing!
Sing like you're coming back from the dead all over again!
He really does care.
Sing!
Sing like you've made it!
You guys, he's right.
Let's sing!
Now music!
Come on!
сказать,
Oh my goodness!
Ah shit!
Let's go!
It murrent!
Oh shit!
LOOK BOO!
Yes!
Two of us!
Number two,
you should be 100%.
Oh
たとえ勝ち目のない戦いでも
夢も覚悟も変わらない
勝負隊の
降伏の
撤退の
撤回を
革命の
接戦の
団結の
速攻を
失望を
屈辱を
失敗を
後悔を
ほのり全て探すの
レッシュを
いつか世界中が見放しても
命の限り
挑もう
決断を
終念を
挽回を
復活を
焦げて
眩しい魂
突きつけろ
終わり
あの
Uh, I think it was close enough.
No way.
Still, it wasn't far removed from what we're known for.
True that.
Hey, Sakura!
Sorry, I wasn't listening.
Don't space out, or I'll kill ya!
Good morning, ladies!
See you again!